Akshay VIjay Pansare Back office Executive

■ akshaypansare0000@gmail.com

9082305918

• Thane, Maharashtra

in www.linkedin.com/in/akkipansare

https://github.com/akkii14

Profile

A seasoned professional with one year of experience in handling wide variety of medical coding and billing tasks. I have a proven track record of delivering exceptional results. My expertise lies in payment posting and billing. Sophisticated and hardworking individual with excellent analytical and multitasking abilities. I am experienced in all aspects of office automation; Strong analytical and numerical abilities. I Function well both independently and as a team member. My goal is to contribute my work ethics & energy to a more positive and growing company where I too can expand my knowledge in a team work environment.

Professional Experience

2021/01 - present Thane, India

Medical Billing - Payment Posting

US Healthcare International Process

- Responsible for timely and accurate posting of payments and adjustments to all patient accounts.
- Interpreted the explanation for benefits (EOB) and balance transfers money to the secondary insurance or patient liability.
- Accountable for daily balancing and tracking of cash and adjustment posting.
- Posted denial information, Efficiently posted payments to the company's accounts receivable systems.
- Posted all electronically available payer remits to appropriate accounts, Posted credit card
 payments electronically or manually as needed.
- Posted all electronic and manual zero pays per Explanation of Benefits, as well as make necessary adjustments to accounts.
- Identified overpayment and notifies collectors for processing according to policy, Posted
 payments to accounts according to the line of service and service dates to ensure accurate
 payment status and accurate account activity according to department process.

2019/06 - 2019/12

Data Entry Clerk

- Entered and verified alphanumeric data from various sources, paper-based, electronic, and phone, into a computer database.
- Interacting with internal department to help fulfil customer request. Entering data into fast field platform
- Maintained accurate and useful database records.
- Tested customer and account system changes and upgrades by inputting new data; reviewing output.
- Entered all client information appropriately on computers.
- Answered incoming telephone calls answers questions about any changes or incorrect patient record.
- Entered Over 400-500 records per day.
- Maintained 99% Accuracy in all data entry tasks ,Used Ms.Excel Daily including Ms.Office.

Courses

2023/01 - present Thane, India

Python Full Stack Developer

Quastech Academy

Frontend - Html Css Javascript Bootstrap Jquery

Framework - Angular Django

Backend - Python Php, Database - MySQL

Education

2019 – 2022/06 Thane, India	Bachelor of Science in Computer Science Mulund College Of Commerce • Mumbai, Maharashtra Passed with 8.65 CGPI with A Grade.
2017 – 2019/04 Thane, India	HSC B.N Bandodkar College Of Science • Thane, Maharashtra Passed with 60.46% in Science Stream with PCMB as subject
2017 Thane, India	SSC Dr. Bedekar Vidya Mandir • Thane, Maharashtra Passed with 83.40% in Maharashtra State Board

Skills

Problem solving	Typing skills
-----------------	---------------

Time management Computer proficiency

Communication skills Adaptability
Attention to detail Multitasking

Certificates

Computer Typing

GCC-TBC English 30 wpm GCC-TBC English 40 wpm

Awards

2023/10/19	The Star Employee SVP, Revenue Optimization Services Awarded for consistently give a top-notch performance.
2023/09/13	IKS Springboard 2023-24 - Carrom Tournament
	The Winner Of Carrom Tournament (Men's Single)
2023/05/29	Certificate Of Graduation
	Revenue Optimization Services
	Awarded for successfully completing the training program
2023/08/08	The Ace Employee
	Revenue optimization services
	Awarded for the best employee in the organization or department.

Projects

Soap Shop Website

- It is a php basedproject with html,css,js,bootstrap used asfrontend and php,mysql as backend.
- Developed this project for Semester 5

Castle Defender Game

- Developed this game in Sublime using Python Language and for backend I used MySql.
- I used MySql Database to save Scores , High Score.
- Castle defender is endless castle defense game , whose goal is to attack on enemy and destroy all enemies before they reached to the castle tower

Declaration

I hereby declare that above information is correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.